I am Ayaka Yasumoto, attendance number 5 at Ebisu Junior High School in the city of Ebisu.
I am Ayaka from Amehera City. Pleased to meet you.
Today, I would like to bring you a dialogue between the two of us.
I look forward to working with you.
But Ayaka and I were together at the chorus battle, and it was there that I finally had a chance to talk with her. Hey, hey, hey. We practiced together every week at the chorus battle, and we got to know each other a little bit, didn't we?
Oh, yes, but we didn't move much.
But we didn't move much.
You made a group, but it didn't work.
It's very common for things not to work.
That's true. We exchanged lines, but not much.
Not much.
Yes, that's true.
I'm so self-conscious about it.
I wish I could have done it myself.
I can tell by your shyness.
Many Amefurashi are shy. We're all shy.
Yuzu has an image of being aggressive.
I heard that when you go to a festival like StarPlaza where everyone is there, you tend to be withdrawn.
That's a little bit similar to EBITCHU.
I thought, "I can smell the same thing from a distance.
We all thought that the children of Amefurashi were just like us.
Oh my God, that's great, but if that's what you think...
I hope you don't think I'm being cheeky.
I'm sure we'll both understand each other now... and we'll get along better next time.
Let's get along.
Please, let's get along.
I'd like to think back to when we first met.
I don't know...
I don't know when it was.
But it was before my wife... when Ira was still working as a day laborer.
I don't mean to be rude if I've mistaken you for someone else, but I didn't do the flower-poki-porch thing.
I remember she said her nose was fluttering and she was doing it.
I'm sorry, but I didn't do the flower poke-poke.
I don't know, maybe I'm remembering wrong.
Maybe some of the other members did.
That's so rude.
Not at all.
I was under the impression that was your specialty.
That's right. She's probably the one left.
Oh, left over. Oh, right, right.
Then it wasn't.
I wonder when, though.
I wonder when.
But as an outdoor festival.
You know, an outdoor festival or something.
It was before Stardust had the Staplefest or something.
It was an event where all the Stardust idols gathered somehow.
Yes, that might have been the case.
That means it's been a decade or so ago.
That's right, it's been about 10 years.
Surprisingly.
Surprisingly...
I'm not sure if it's unexpectedly bad or not.
The time when Dori joined was right around the time we were talking about.
Right... that's right... it was the same year that miniatures had their first original song...
There were a lot of songs like the miniature cheering song and "100" and so on, right?
In the beginning, we didn't really have any music, so we just started cheering for the team.
Let's go!
And just when we finally got to the point where we could dance to the music, we had to quit.
I was about 9 years old when I joined the miniatures, so it was more like a lesson than a career in the arts.
So when I was suddenly asked to sing at a summer festival or something, I would say something like "touch" or "I'm in love with your eyes," and we'd all just go "let's go.
I had always been attracted to cheerleading and so on.
I had an image of cheerleading, and I thought it would suit me.
I've always wanted to be a cheerleader.
But maybe I was too.
Did you have some kind of a presentation for your mother to watch?
What?
You were a cheerleading base?
I don't know if we had a recital for my mom to watch, but we would practice the day before we went out in front of the fans, and then we would go to the studio.
You know that studio with the magic mirror?
There's a studio with a magic mirror... where the mothers can look through the mirror and watch the show.
It's really bad!
It was like a real school. It was like a real lesson.
It was a hell of a time, wasn't it? It was embarrassing and humiliating to be seen by your mother.
It was a red cart like they used in acting lessons.
We'd do it during break time.
Some of the girls were doing it even though it was past break time.
I used to do that too.
I was always being scolded for it.
I thought it was a scary thing.
We were playing with it?
We were all in elementary school or something.
So before the show started and when it was over.
We did that before and after the show, didn't we?
We did!
It was like a signal to switch, and then we'd take a break and practice.
We did that, but then we were kids, so we couldn't switch back and forth, so we were always getting in trouble.
I'm the same... and I'm the same... and I'm the same... and I'm the same... and I'm the same... and I eat this at every break.
I'm going to break up the break time and munch a little bit on something...
I'm not going to make it in time to eat anything.
I only have this image of being pissed off.
I think a lot of them like squid and other greedy things.
I don't know... even after I joined EBITCHU, I'm still very much a hit-or-miss kind of girl.
They all like squid.
I love it!
I think they like smoked squid, so I think that's why they're so picky.
I like people who want it.
You like people who want things. - No.
No, they have something in common... something they're not supposed to have in common.
I just talked to my makeup artist, and she told me about the gym... and how she's been touching her personal stuff.
I'm glad you're being a little cautious, because I'm a little embarrassed to admit that I'm just starting out.
I'm just starting out. I love saunas and gun baths.
I love it, too. I'm just starting out.
And I started going to the gym because it has a sauna.
Oh, yeah? Where do you work out?
Are you working out more upper body now, where there's some human muscle mass? Right now I'm working out more upper body muscles, you know, human muscles.
Chest, back, abs.
And legs, like squats.
Big muscles.
I'm also doing a lot of running right now.
That's great.
I'm not really good at cardio.
I know, right?
It's impossible.
It's really hard.
I used to be able to run for 10 minutes and now I can run for 20 minutes.
I can't run anymore, so I gave it up. I've been kickboxing lately.
I've been kickboxing and doing cardio there.
We've had a lot of girl talk... and then we'll go back to talking about groups.
We're celebrating our 15th anniversary this August.
And last November was our 5th anniversary... which means we're celebrating our 5th anniversary.
In the sense of anniversary, that's one thing we have in common.
From tomorrow onwards, each of you will be an interviewer, and I would like to hear what you have to say.
I'm nervous, aren't you?
That's all for now, Ayaka Yasumoto from Ebiichi Municipal Junior High School and Ayana Amehura from Amehura City.
That's Ayaka Yasumoto from Eimichi Municipal Junior High School and Ayana from Amehra City.
See you tomorrow!